cvapor.com 2019-04-21

# Security and Privacy - Cvapor.com

Last updated: May 24th, 2018

This privacy policy only applies to www.cvapor.com (quoted as ‘Site’ below). We will comply with it, as well as applicable Privacy laws, when we gather and use information from users of the Site. We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy to understand how we collect information and what we do with the information we collect from you.

**A. Information Collected**

This privacy policy applies only to information collected on the Site. The information we collect depends on the context of your interactions with us, the choices you make, including your privacy settings, and the products and features you use on Site.

We collect two types of information from visitors to the Site: (1) Personally Identifiable Information; and (2) Non-Personally Identifiable Information, such as Browser version, IP address, Device information, etc.

(1) Personal Identifiable Information

"Personal Identifiable Information" is the information that identifies you personally, such as your name, date of birth, address, telephone number, email address, or company name. The Site collects and stores the personally identifiable information that you have provided to us. Here are some examples of manners in which we may collect your personally identifiable information on the Site:

We may collect your first name, last name, address, email address, telephone number, company, country, and the type for your question or comment when you fill out a “Contact Us” form on our Site;

We may collect your first and last name, date of birth and email address if you choose to participate in our giveaway activities; We may collect your first and last name, your address, and your credit card and billing information if you make a purchase of a product or service.

If you are a customer, you will typically provide your name, address, email address, telephone number to be able to communicate with us about the products and services we offer to you. If you do not want us to collect your personal identifiable information, please do not provide it to us.

(2) Non-Personal Identifiable Information

We also collect other information that is not personally identifiable to you, but results solely from your visit to the Site. "Non-Personal Identifiable Information" can be technical information or it can be demographic information, such as SDK/API/JS code version, browser, Internet service provider, IP address, platform, timestamp, application identifier, application version, application distribution channel, etc. Here are some examples of the non-personal identifiable information that is collected via the site and a description of how this information is used:

Internet Protocol (IP) address: Your IP address is usually associated with the place from which you enter the Internet. We use this information to deliver our web pages to you upon request, to tailor our Site to the interests of our users and to measure traffic within our Site.

Cookies: “Cookies” are bits of electronic information that can be transferred to your computer or other electronic device to uniquely identify your browser. We may use cookies to connect your activity on the Site with other information we store about you in your account profile or your prior interactions on the Site, for example, store your preferences. The cookies enable the Site to facilitate access to different aspects of the website. For example, by showing when and how you and others visit its website, cookies help the Site to see which pages are popular and which are not. Cookies can also help the Site to improve your enjoyment of this website, for example, by remembering your address or other personal information when you request information or services on the website. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can disable this function so that your browser will not accept cookies. Please be aware that disabling this function may impact your use and enjoyment of this website.

Web Beacons are Internet tools, such as transparent images on a website or in e-mails that we may send you, that helps to determine, for instance, the number of visitors to the Site, whether a page has been viewed or an e-mail opened, or to collect other related information, and this information may be associated with your unique browser, device identifier, or IP address. For example, when you ask us to send you information on a promotion or newsletter, we may use web beacons to determine how many of the e-mails we sent were actually opened. In general, any electronic image viewed as part of a web page, including a banner ad, can contain a web beacon.

Demographic Information: "Demographic Information" may be your gender, age, zip code and interests, which you voluntarily provide to us on the Site. We use this information to provide you with personalized services and to analyze trends to ensure the information provided by the Site to satisfy your needs. For example, if you subscribe to a specific newsletter, cvapor.com may collect your zip code or interests. Please note that we also consider aggregated information, which is not personally identifiable, to be non-personally identifiable information. The above list provides an example of the non-personally identifiable information that is collected via the Site.

We collect the above non-personally identifiable information from all visitors to our Site. If you do not want us to have access to those information, please do not visit our Site.

**B. Use of Information Collected Via the Site**

We use information that is collected on the Site primarily for the following purposes:

To respond to your enquiry, ask a question, contact you about your request or other reasons related to offering and improving our products and services;

To operate, evaluate, and improve our products and service;

To complete a transaction or service requested by you;

To perform market research;

To advertise and market our products and solutions;

To help us create and publish content most relevant to you;

To analyze our products and services and our Site;

To allow you access to limited-entry areas of the Site;

To improve our security and administer our Site.

**C. Sharing and Disclosure of Information**

We may share any information we collect, including Personal Information with the following categories of recipients and/or in the following circumstances:

As appropriate, we may share any information, including Personal Information, with any of our group companies, vendors or service providers in connection with the provision or marketing of the Services. These third parties have access to Personal Information to the extent necessary to permit them to do their jobs, however, they are bound by confidentiality agreements before any information is provided to them, and they are restricted from using the information for other purposes.

As Required by Law and Similar Disclosures, we may access, preserve, and disclose information, including Personal Information, if we believe it is necessary: to comply with national security or law enforcement requests and legal process, such as a court order or subpoena; to respond to your requests; to prevent or address fraud, security, or technical issues; or to protect our property or other legal rights or the rights or property of others, or to protect the vital interests of others.

If we are involved in a merger, acquisition, financing, reorganization, bankruptcy, receivership, sale of company assets, or transition of service to another provider, information collected through the Site may be sold or transferred as part of such a transaction, as permitted by law and/or contract

To protect against potential fraud, we may verify with third parties the information collected from the Site. In the course of such verification, we may receive personal identifiable information about you from such services.

Other than as stated in this Privacy Policy or at the time we request the information, we will not release Personal Information to unaffiliated third parties, and we will not cross-reference Personal Information collected through one client’s use of our Site with that of any other client or entity.

**D. Legal Basis for Information Processing**

We process Personal and Non-Personal Identifiable Information for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy, as described above. Our legal basis to process personal information includes processing that is: necessary for the performance of the contract with you; necessary to comply with legal requirements; necessary for our legitimate interests; and based on consent by our customers.

**E. Visitors Under the Age of 18**

We do not knowingly collect, store, or use information from those visitors/users under the age of 18. We have clear notification on the Site to alert any visitors/users under the age of 18 not to visit/use our Site. However, if we learn that such behaviors happened on our Site (due to accident click or intentionally cheat), any information, Personal or Non-Personal Identifiable Information will be deleted or destroyed.

**F. Opt-Out**

You have the right to opt-out of marketing communications we send you at any time. In addition to using our contact details below, for email marketing communications you can exercise this right by clicking on the “unsubscribe” or “opt-out” link in the marketing e-mails we send you.

**G. Third Party Web Sites**

This privacy policy applies solely to information collected on the Site. The Site may contain links to other web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these other web sites. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of such websites or applications before disclosing your personal information to them.

**H. Third Party Advertisers**

We may use advertisers, third party ad networks, and other advertising companies, to serve advertisements on the Site. Please be advised that such advertising companies may gather information about your visit to the Site or other sites (such as through cookies, web beacons and other technologies) to enable such advertising companies to market products or services to you, to monitor which ads have been served to your browser and which web pages you were viewing when such ads were delivered.

**I. Assignment**

In the event that all or part of our assets are sold or acquired by another party, or in the event of a merger, you grant us the right to assign the personal identifiable and non-personal identifiable information collected via the Site.

**J. Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to modify or amend this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make changes, we will notify you by revising the date at the top of this Privacy Policy and, in some cases, we may provide you with additional notice. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy whenever you access our websites to stay informed about our information practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy.

**K. Security**

We will take reasonable measures to help secure your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure in accordance with generally accepted principles for the storage of personal data. These measures are designed to provide a level of security appropriate to the risk of processing of your personal information. However, neither the Internet nor any form of electronic storage can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, and we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information provided to us.

Please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of such firewalls and secure server software.

If you have any questions, comments, or concerns about this privacy policy or our privacy practices, please contact us at [cooperate@cvapor.com](mailto:cooperate@cvapor.com) . All information you provide in any written communication will also be covered by this policy.
